New Day, new security.  Today we will talk about
Sunlife's new and great product.  Sunlife Save
and Protect Plus.
Numbers to remember so
we can understand this product.
20 7 5 and 140%.
20 because your protection is for 20 years.
7 because you only need to multiply
your annual premium to get the
protection you want.  But if
you have a number in mind, you want to
have specific protection,
you can divide that coverage by
seven to find out how much
annual premium I need to pay
to get said protection.
Then five for 5 years to pay.  There is no
other choice.  Payments have only been made for 5 years
.
Then, we just multiply
our total premium paid by 140 to
get the total guaranteed maturity
benefit or money back.  Now let
's give a number.  For example, a client's
annual premium is Php100,000.
To get his insurance
benefit, we just multiply this by 7
and he will have 700,000
guaranteed life insurance protection on
day 1 of his insurance and it will
last for 20 years.
Then if his annual insurance
premium is Php100,000,
we multiply this by 5 years to
get his total insurance
premium paid.
Look, you only paid for 5 years
but you will be given 7 years, seven times the
protection of Sunlight.  7 times the
annual premium paid.  So here's just
500,000 total premium paid but
your insurance coverage is 700,000.
So he has an adjustment or
you have an advantage of Php2,000.
And that's not all.  What if you outlive
your insurance after 20 years?  You didn't
use the insurance.
Is your money wasted?  No.  Because
Sunlife's promise is that it will refund 140% of the
total premium paid.  So 500,000
140%
you can expect Php700,000.
And that's not all, there is more.
We also have something called a living benefit.
This is the plan we can use
as long as we live.  When
we need money, we can
take out a loan.
Then we also have what is called a
terminal illness benefit which is 60% of
the face amount.  This means that if
we are diagnosed with a terminal illness,
we can use the plant and
we can withdraw money for treatment.
Oh, right?  Let's see, once
we have an actual illustration, how do
we number it?  So, here
our coverage is 20 years from year 1
to 20. We are covered by life insurance.
In our actual illustration, the client
paid 71,429
and Sunlimes promised
an annual premium.  That will be the
insurance coverage or death benefit.
Get the calculator.  Check.  71,429
* 7 = 500,000.
And isn't that the only
promise of Sunl? You only pay for 5 years,
so when the fifth year comes,
the basic premium paid will no longer
increase.  That's it, because
you're only guaranteed to pay for 5 years,
but your coverage is for 20 years.  What if
on the 10th year you need money?
You can withdraw from this
guaranteed cash value and use this
for emergencies.
Aside from
this, you can also use
your face amount, the 500,000
just in case we have a terminal
illness, multiply it by 60%.  So
you can expect something from this plan while you
are alive, undergoing treatment, there will be
300,000 given
from this plan.  And that's not all.
What if after 20 years we are still alive.   Was
the 357.14 I paid a waste?
Because Sunlife's promise is not,
I will refund you 140%
of the total premium paid.  So take the
calculator again.  357.14
140%.
Will this plan give you
half a million after 20 years?
How would you feel if the insurance
you buy for your family was
not only for your family but
also for you to benefit from while you
were still alive?
And how much more?  If you outlive
the insurance duration,
you will still get guaranteed
cash of
more than 40% more than what
you paid.
How would you feel after 20 years if
you only had half a million to expect
from this plan?